A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Hong Kong Arts Program, Record Group 6 FA1436
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Photographs, 1986-2006; 2
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Ken Friedenberg and HK Sinfonietta, Photo print and slides (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - Kam Wing Chong, Photo print and slides (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 1998 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 1999 ACC Events Photos - Helene Liu Party, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Cheung Mei, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Catherine Yau, Photo print (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Alex Tam, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Andy Lam, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Jiao Xiaojian, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Ren Ming, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Wong Shun Kit, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Priscilla Leung, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1999 ACC Grantees Photos - Olivia Yan, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 2000 ACC Events Photos - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Photo print (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 2000 ACC Events Photos - ACC Arts Salon - Une Soiree pour les Beaux Arts at Jebsen's Residence, 2000 November 9; Photo print (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 2000 ACC Events Photos - ACC Arts Salon - Une Soiree pour les Beaux Arts at Jebsen's Residence, 2000 November 9; Photo print (Box 13, Folder 1-7)
  - 2000 ACC Events Photos - ACC Arts Salon - Une Soiree pour les Beaux Arts at Jebsen's Residence, 2000 November 9; Photo print (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - 2000 ACC Events Photos - Dr. Deanna Rudgard Farewell Party, 2000 December 4; Photo print (Box 14, Folder 3-7)
  - 2000 ACC Events Photos - Brenda Chow's Farewell Party, 2000 December 18; Photo print (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - 2000 ACC Events Photos - Brenda Chow's Farewell Party, 2000 December 18; Photo print (Box 15, Folder 1-5)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Awards Ceremony, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Chan Ping Chiu, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Florence Pui Shan Cheung, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - BAT Grantees, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Yap Man Shan, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Betsy Cheung, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Wang Yi, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Liang Bibo, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Ho Siu Kee, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Tse Kwan Ho, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Annie Lai Kuen Wan, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - San Jie Cao by Bibo Liang, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Tang Shu Wing Cultural Exchange Project Grant, Photo print (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 2000 ACC Grantees Photos - Arzuni and Prof. Wu, Photo print (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 2001 ACC Events Photos - Friends Committee Meeting, 2001 June 26; Photo print (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 2001 ACC Events Photos - Grantees and Friends Meeting, Photo print (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 2001 ACC Grantees Photos - Suen Wan Ting, Photo print (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 2001 ACC Grantees Photos - So Yan Kei, Photo print (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 2001 ACC Grantees Photos - Tu Yuliang, Photo print (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 2001 ACC Grantees Photos - Aenon Loo Jia-En, Photo print (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 2001 ACC Grantees Photos - Mak Hon Ming Franky, Photo print (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 2001 ACC Grantees Photos - Tseng Sun Man, Photo print (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 2001 ACC Grantees Photos - Xiong Yuanwei, Photo print (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 2001 ACC Grantees Photos - Grantees Party, Photo print (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Howard Gardner Visit to Tai Po Old Market Primary School, 2002 January 25; Photo print (Box 17, Folder 3-8)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Howard Gardner Presentation at CUHK Book 1-2, 2002 January 25; Photo print (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Howard Gardner Visit to Hong Kong Museum of Art Book 1-2, 2002 January 27; Photo print (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Howard Gardner Visit - ACC Party at Jebsen's Residence Book 1-3, 2002 January 27; Photo print (Box 18, Folder 5-7)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Howard Gardner Luncheon Presentation at Madarin Oriental, Book 1, 2002 January 28; Photo print (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Howard Gardner Luncheon Presentation at Madarin Oriental, Book 2-5, 2002 January 28; Photo print (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos, Photo print (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - ACC Fellowship Award Presentation Evening, Book 1-2, 2002 June 20; Photo print (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - ACC Fellowship Award Presentation Evening, Book 3, 2002 June 20; Photo print (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos, Photo prints and negatives (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Board Trip to China, Book 1-2B, 2002 November 3-10; Photo print (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Board Trip to China, Book 3-5A, 2002 November 3-10; Photo print (Box 20, Folder 6-8)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Board Trip to China, Book 5B-7, 2002 November 3-10; Photo print (Box 20, Folder 9-11)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Board Trip to China Book 8-10, 2002 November 3-10; Photo print (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
  - 2002 ACC Events Phots - Board Trip to China Book 11-13, 2002 November 3-10; Photo print (Box 21, Folder 4-6)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Board Trip to China, 2002 November 3-10; Photo print (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - Meeting with Chief Executive C. H. Tung, 2002 November 11; Photo print (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - ACC in China Reception at Jebsen's Residence Book A-D, 2002 November 11; Photo print (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - ACC in China Reception at Jebsen's Residence Book E-F, 2002 November 11; Photo print (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
  - 2002 ACC Events Photos - ACC in China Reception, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - John Lee Yiu Shing, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - Hung Wing Kit, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - Lio Kuok Man, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - Sandy Leung Siu Ying, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - Tim Li Man Wai, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - Leung Mee Ping, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - Zheng Tianwei, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - Hu Rongrui, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - 2002 ACC Grantees Photos - Meng Jinghui, Photo print (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - 2003 ACC Events Photos - ACC Fellowship Award Reception, Roll A-C, 2003 June 27; Photo print (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
  - 2003 ACC Events Photos - ACC Fellowship Awards Reception, Roll D-E, 2003 June 27; Photo print (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
  - 2003 ACC Events Photos - 2003 Fellowship Awards Reception, Photo print (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 2003 ACC Events Photos - On Stage with Kenneth Fung at Sir Gordon and Lady Wu's Residence, Roll A-B, 2003 December 5; Photo print (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - 2003 ACC Events Photos - On Stage with Kenneth Fung at Sir Gordon and Lady Wu's Residence, Roll C-I, 2003 December 5; Photo prints and negatives (Box 24, Folder 1-8)
  - 2004 ACC Events Photos - ACC Fellowship Award Ceremony, Book 1-5, 2004 June 24; Photo print (Box 25, Folder 1-6)
  - 2004 ACC Events Photos - Welcome Reception for Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater at Jebsen's Residence, Roll A, Photo print (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - 2004 ACC Events Photos - Welcome Reception for Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater at Jebsen's Residence, Roll B-G, 2004 October 8; Photo print (Box 26, Folder 1-7)
  - 2004 ACC Events Photos - ACC-New York Gala Event, 2004 November 10; Photo print (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 2004 ACC Events Photos - Question and Answer Session, 2004 December 11; Photo print (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 2005 ACC Events Photos - Exhibition of works by Hon Chi Fun at Hong Kong Museum of Art, Roll A-D, 2005 April 21; Photo print (Box 27, Folder 3-6)
  - 2005 ACC Events Photos - Exhibition of works by Hon Chi Fun at Hong Kong Museum of Art, Roll E-F, 2005 April 21; Photo prints and negatives (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
  - 2005 ACC Events Photos - ACC Award Ceremony, Exhibition, and Dinner with J. S. Lee, "Crossing Boundaries" at the Lee Gardens, Roll A-E, 2005 September 27; Photo print (Box 28, Folder 4-8)
  - 2005 ACC Events Photos - ACC Award Ceremony, Exhibition, and Dinner with J. S. Lee, "Crossing Boundaries" at the Lee Gardens, Roll F-G, 2005 September 27; Photo print (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - 2005 ACC Events Photos - ACC Award Ceremony and Exhibition, "Crossing Boundaries" at the Lee Gardens, Photo print (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 2005 ACC Events Photos - Friends' Trip to Xinhui and Kaiping, Book 1-3, 2005 November 4-6; Photo print (Box 29, Folder 4-6)
  - 2005 ACC Grantees Photos - Untitled Album, Photo print (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 2005 ACC Grantees Photos - Untitled Album, Photo print (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - 2006 ACC Events Photos - Exhibition of works by Elizabeth Gill Lui at UMA G and Sau Wah Fong Gallery, Roll A-E, 2006 March 27; Photo print (Box 30, Folder 3-7)
  - 2006 ACC Events Photos - Exhibition of works by Elizabeth Gill Lui at UMA G and Sau Wah Fong Gallery, Roll F, 2006 March 27; Photo print (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 2006 ACC Events Photos - Exhibition of works by Elizabeth Gill Lui, Photo print (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 2006 ACC Events Photos - Award Ceremony, Exhibition, and Dinner at the Lee Gardens, Roll A-F, 2006 October 26; Photo print (Box 31, Folder 3-8)
  - 2006 ACC Events Photos - Award Ceremony and Exhibition at the Lee Gardens, Roll G, 2006 October 26; Photo print (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - AGFA Grant, Photo print (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - AIWA Grant, Photo print (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - BAT Grant, Book A-C, Photo print (Box 32, Folder 5-7)
  - BAT Grant, 1987-2000; Photo prints and slides (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - BAT Grant 10th Anniversary, 1996; Photo print (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - BAT Grant 10th Anniversary, 1996; Photo print (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Hopewell Grant, Photo print (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Hsin Chong Grant, Photo print (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Lee Hysan Grant, Photo print (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Audiovisual Materials, 3
  - ACC Events - Videos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2003 On Stage with Kenneth Fung, 2003 December 5; VHS tape (Box T1)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - ACC Events - Videos - ACC-Hong Kong: 20th Anniversary Celebration - ACC Celebrates 20 Years in Hong Kong - 3 Minute Trailer- FINAL, 2008 January 18; DVD (Box T1)
  - ACC Events - Videos - ACC-Hong Kong: ACC Grantee Video Clips in 2002 - Edited by Yeung Hei (2002), 2002 January 28; VHS tape: master (Box T1)
  - ACC Events - Videos - ACC-Hong Kong:2002 Board Trip to China from Bibo Liang ? Unedited First Version without Music (PAL), 2002 November 3-10; VHS tape: master (Box T1)
  - ACC Events - Videos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2002 Board Trip to China from Bibo Liang- Second Version (Pal System: 40), 2002 November 3-10; VHS tape: master (Box T1)
  - ACC Events - Videos - ACC-Hong Kong: 1996 Chen Kaige Excerpts, 1996 November; Betacam: master (Box T1)
  - ACC - Events - Videos - ACC-New York: 2004 ACC 40th Anniversary Reel, 2004 November 10; VHS tape: master (Box T1)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 1998 Award Reception - Moving Image, 1998 June; Digital video: master (Box T2)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Trip- WEI Ligang and TIAN Mansha in NY - Moving Image, 2005-2006; Digital video: master (Box T2)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Trip- Rani Khanam Part I - Moving Image, 2006 July; Digital video: master (Box T2)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: Grantee Trip- Rani Khanam Part II - Moving Image, 2006 July; Digital video: master (Box T2)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: 2007 ACC Documentary Film- FINAL- NO music, 2007 October 2; Digital video: master (Box T2)
  - ACC Events - Videos and Photos - ACC-Hong Kong: ACC Photo Montage FINAL- RAW Version, 2007 October 9; Digital video: master (Box T2)